Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.14
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Campaign for U.S. Senate, 1991; XIV.
  - Campaign in Progress, 3.
    - Media
      - Media advisories sent regarding Thornburgh's campaign schedule, August 27-October 31, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 5)
      - White House Bulletin, coverage of Attorney General Thornburgh's candidacy for Senate, June 4-November 4, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 6)
      - Pennsylvania Report, coverage of Thornburgh's candidacy for Senate, August-October, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 7)
      - Thornburgh campaign press kits, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Issue Statements
      - Positions on health care and fast track authority, September 3, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 9)
      - Thornburgh's record on helping veterans, September 10, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 10)
      - "Thornburgh's Commitment to Persons with Disabilities", September 16, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 11)
      - "Thornburgh urges Congressional Support for School Reform Initiatives", September 18, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 12)
      - "Thornburgh's Assistance to Small Businesses", September 19, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 13)
      - "Thornburgh Calls for 'Industrial Renaissance' Initiative to Create Jobs at Abandoned Industrial Sites", September 23, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 14)
      - "Dick Thornburgh: Fighting for Lower Taxes", September 25, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 15)
      - Letter to Editor of Pittsburgh Post-Gazette from Dan Eramian, spokesman for Thornburgh for Senate, regarding civil rights issues, September 27, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 16)
      - "Testimony of Dick Thornburgh regarding USAir's application for Pittsburgh-Italy service", October 1, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 17)
      - "Dick Thornburgh: Fighting for Jobs", October 3, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 18)
      - "Thornburgh Calls for Federal Enterprise Zone Legislation", October 10, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 19)
      - "Dick Thornburgh is Good for Taxpayers", October 10, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 20)
      - "Thornburgh Urges Prompt Action in Multilateral Steel Agreement to Protect Steel Jobs Against Foreign Competition", October 15, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 21)
      - "Thornburgh Calls for Overhaul of Senate Confirmation Process", October 16, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 22)
      - "Thornburgh issues Six point Plan for Congressional Reform", October 25, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 23)
      - "Thornburgh Calls for Tax Relief for Working Families", October 27, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 24)
      - "Seniors Defend Thornburgh Record", November 2, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 25)
      - "Thornburgh says National Health Insurance Could Cost Pennsylvania Jobs", November 4, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 26)
      - "Fact Sheet: Dick Thornburgh and Harris Wofford", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 27)
      - "Dick Thornburgh's Agenda for the 90s", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 28)
      - "Thornburgh Administration Accomplishments Related to America 2000," national education program introduced by George Bush, May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 29-30)
      - "Dick Thornburgh's Commitment to Basic Education", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 31)
      - Positions on jobs, unemployment compensation, taxes, abortion, health care, foreign trade, family leave, gun control, Social Security, education and transportation (includes Rick Stafford's notes), May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 32)
      - "Dick Thornburgh's Proposals to Create and Preserve Jobs in Pennsylvania", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 33)
      - "Straight Talk about Dick Thornburgh's Record of Helping Senior Citizens", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 34)
      - "Dick Thornburgh: Protecting Our Environment", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 35)
      - "Thornburgh Environmental Position" and "Snapshot of the Thornburgh Environmental Record", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 36)
      - "Dick Thornburgh's 14-Point Plant Plan for Affordable Health Care," Thornburgh and Wofford's positions and background material, May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 37)
      - "Responsible Health Care Reform," essay by Dick Thornburgh, candidate for United States Senate, May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 38)
      - "Bank of Credit Commerce International (BCCI) Facts", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 39)
      - "Fact Sheet: Working People", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 40)
      - "Dick Thornburgh: Leadership on the Issues", May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 41)
      - Positions on issues concerning Philadelphia, PA, July-September, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 42)
      - Positions on issues concerning Pittsburgh, PA, August, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 43)
      - Positions and research on the Jewish community, 1990-1991 (Box 913, Folder 44)
      - Thornburgh positions, May-November, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 45)
      - Thornburgh campaign responses and defenses of record in response to Wofford attacks, August-October, 1991 (Box 913, Folder 46)
    - Campaign Statements regarding Harris Wofford
      - "Harris Wofford and the Savings and Loan Crooks", May-November, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 1)
      - "Did Bryn Mawr College Have a Deficit While Harris Wofford was President?", May-November, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 2)
      - "Straight Talk About National Health Insurance," letter from U.S. Congressmen, letter to editor with corrections, and memorandum, May-November, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 3)
      - "Harris Wofford: Pennsylvania's Last Choice for the U.S. Senate Seat," preliminary opposition research binder prepared by Thornburgh campaign, May 23, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 4)
      - "Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania: Senator Wofford in Violation of Federal Law", September 4, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 5)
      - "State GOP questions Wofford fund raising," Philadelphia Inquirer, September 6, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Briefing Binders
      - Thornburgh's briefing binder, regarding positions, Wofford, issues research and strategy reports (annotated), May-November, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 7-9)
      - Items removed from Thornburgh's campaign briefing binder, July-August, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 10)
      - Research and issue material, prepared by Harold Miller, August 17, 1991 (Box 914, Folder 11)
      - "Work plan and Defensive Issues Paper," prepared by Harold Miller, July 4, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 1)
    - Fundraising
      - Lists of donors, September 20, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 2)
      - Fundraising events and plans, September-November, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 3)
      - Campaign contributions, report of receipts and disbursements, August-September, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 4-6)
      - Fundraising and reimbursement receipts, 1991-1992 (Box 915, Folder 7)
      - Federal Election Commission (FEC) reports, August 16, 1991-June 30, 2002 (Box 915, Folder 8)
    - County Briefing Materials
      - Adams, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 9)
      - Allegheny, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 10)
      - Armstrong, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 11)
      - Beaver, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 12)
      - Bedford, 1991 (Box 915, Folder 13)
      - Berks, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 1)
      - Blair, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 2)
      - Bradford, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 3)
      - Bucks, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 4)
      - Butler, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 5)
      - Cambria, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 6)
      - Cameron, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 7)
      - Carbon, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 8)
      - Centre, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 9)
      - Chester, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 10)
      - Clarion, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 11)
      - Clearfield, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 12)
      - Clinton, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 13)
      - Columbia, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 14)
      - Crawford, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 15)
      - Cumberland, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 16)
      - Dauphin, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 17)
      - Delaware, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 18)
      - Elk, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 19)
      - Erie, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 20)
      - Forest, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 21)
      - Franklin, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 22)
      - Fulton, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 23)
      - Greene, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 24)
      - Huntingdon, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 25)
      - Indiana, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 26)
      - Jefferson, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 27)
      - Juniata, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 28)
      - Lackawanna, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 29)
      - Lancaster, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 30)
      - Lawrence, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 31)
      - Lebanon, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 32)
      - Lehigh, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 33)
      - Luzerne, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 34)
      - Lycoming, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 35)
      - McKean, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 36)
      - Mercer, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 37)
      - Mifflin, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 38)
      - Monroe, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 39)
      - Montgomery, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 40)
      - Montour, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 41)
      - Northampton, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 42)
      - Perry, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 43)
      - Pike, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 44)
      - Philadelphia, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 45)
      - Potter, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 46)
      - Schuylkill, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 47)
      - Snyder, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 48)
      - Somerset, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 49)
      - Sullivan, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 50)
      - Susquehanna, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 51)
      - Tioga, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 52)
      - Union, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 53)
      - Venango, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 54)
      - Warren, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 55)
      - Washington, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 56)
      - Wayne, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 57)
      - Westmoreland, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 58)
      - Wyoming, 1991 (Box 916, Folder 59)
      - York, 1991 (Box 917, Folder 1)
    - Alphabetical Correspondence
      - A-Z, August-November, 1991 (Box 917, Folder 2-25)
      - A-Z, December, 1991-January, 1992 (Box 917, Folder 26-27)
    - Election Results and Post-election Analysis
      - Thank you calls to be made by the Governor, November 2, 1991 (Box 918, Folder 1)
      - Election results newspaper coverage, Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, November 7, 1991 (Box 918, Folder 2)
      - Media Team's and other analyses of campaign and defeat, November 20, 1991 (Box 918, Folder 3)
      - "White House Bulletin" and Mike Berman's "Washington Political Watch," analyses of election results, December, 1991-July, 1992 (Box 918, Folder 4)
    - Articles and News Clippings regarding Thornburgh, Casey and Wofford
      - Thornburgh's Gubernatorial record, 1979-1987 (Box 918, Folder 5-12)
      - Articles from end of Thornburgh administration ("administration positives"), January, 1987 (Box 918, Folder 13)
      - Card file indexing positive and negative news clippings regarding Dick Thornburgh, Harris Wofford and Robert Casey, 1986-1991 (Box 918, Folder 14)
      - Positive and negative news clippings regarding Dick Thornburgh, Harris Wofford, and Robert Casey, 1986 (Box 918, Folder 15)
      - Donald Mazziotti and William Keisling, officials in the Casey administration, February-October, 1987 (Box 918, Folder 16)
      - Positive and negative news clippings regarding Dick Thornburgh, Harris Wofford, and Robert Casey, 1987-1991 (Box 918, Folder 17-43)
  - Questionnaires, 4.
    Before an election, it is common for newspapers and varying other organizations to request from candidates either responses to questionnaires or specific position statements. The questions asked reflect the group's interests in some way and/or are designed to present views of the candidates to the voting public. The answers that the candidates provide may lead to campaign endorsements, but the information almost always is shared with the organization's members or the newspaper's readers.
    The questionnaires are a group of requests from organizations to Dick Thornburgh and, in most cases, his subsequent responses are included. They are arranged alphabetically by organization or publication name.
    - Allentown Morning Call, October 24, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 1)
    - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), October 15, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 2)
    - American Insurance Association, September 12, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 3)
    - American Metal Market, October 29, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 4)
    - Associated Press (AP), October 7, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association, Inc., September 13, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 6)
    - BAND Together for Global Security, October 10, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 7)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, September 23, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 8)
    - Clean Water Action, August 22, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 9)
    - Conservative Victory Fund (CVF), August 16, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 10)
    - Farmer's Friend newspaper, undated (Box 919, Folder 11)
    - Gannet News Service, October 18, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 12)
    - Lancaster County ACTION, September 18, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 13)
    - League of Conservation Voters, August 16, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 14)
    - League of Women Voters, September 3, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 15)
    - National Association of Wholesaler-Distributors, September 17, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 16)
    - National Federation of Independent Business (NFIB) Free Enterprise PAC, September 13, 1991, October 7, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 17)
    - National Right-to-Life, August 21, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania Association for the Education of Young Children (AEYC), October 16, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 19)
    - Pennsylvania Association of Life Underwriters, September 12, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Catholic Conference, September 24, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania Credit Union League, September 16, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 22)
    - Pennsylvania Family Institute, September 1, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 23)
    - Pennsylvania Farmers' Association (PFA), September 4, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania Medical Political Action Committee (PaMPAC), August 29, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 25)
    - Pennsylvania Medical Society, September 23, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 26)
    - Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association (REA) Allegheny Electric Cooperative, Inc., October 10, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 27)
    - Pennsylvania State Education Association Political Action Committee for Education (PSEA-PACE), August 12, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 28)
    - Public Service Research Council, August 22, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 29)
    - Sierra Club, August 2, 1991, August 31, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 30)
    - Snyder, Union and Northumberland (S.U.N.) Counties Chapter of the National Organization of Women, August 22, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 31)
    - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 506, September 17, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 32)
    - Veterans Political Action Council (VPAC), August 14, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 33)
    - Wilkes-Barre Times Leader, October 28, 1991 (Box 919, Folder 34)
  - Schedules and Events, 5.
    Daily and weekly schedules for the campaign are included in this section in addition to the following events.
    The events for the campaign date from August 19, 1991 to November 5, 1991. These events contain background information for press announcements, meetings, and editorial boards. They also such items as conferences, rallies, festivals, interviews, meetings, county receptions, walking tours, trade fairs, and even pig roasts. There is a board range of issues and constituencies, for example: senior citizens, disabilities, health care, economic development and business enterprise zones. There are also several fundraising events, sponsored by the Thornburgh for Senate Committee (TSC). The events well represent the commitment of Candidate Thornburgh.
    - Schedules
      - Daily Schedules, August-November, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 1)
      - Weekly Schedules, August-November, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 2)
    - Events
      - Press conference at Rehabilitation Institute of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, August 19, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 3)
      - Pittsburgh media interviews, Pittsburgh, August 20, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 4)
      - Funeral service for Mercer Tate, Mt. Airy, August 20, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 5)
      - Pennyback Woods Community Center, remarks, Philadelphia, August 22, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 6)
      - PMA reception and meeting with Philadelphia business leaders, Philadelphia, August 22, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 7)
      - Meeting with Montgomery County Republican leaders, Norristown, August 23, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 8)
      - Lycoming County Republican committee picnic with brief remarks, Williamsport, August 25, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 9)
      - Reception in honor of Senator Charlie Lemmond, Dallas, August 25, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 10)
      - Meeting with employees at Precision Industries, Inc., Washington, August 26, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 11)
      - Walking tour of Main Street with County Commissioner Ed Paluso, Washington, August 26, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 12)
      - Meeting with Harold Miller regarding briefing materials, Pittsburgh, August 26, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 13)
      - Meetings with Evans Rose and CEOs of private companies, Pittsburgh, August 27, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 14)
      - K&L partners luncheon, Pittsburgh, August 27, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 15)
      - National Rehabilitation Week, Presentation of the Senator John Heinz Memorial Legislative Award, Washington, DC, August 28, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 16)
      - Statewide Candidacy Announcement, multiple locations, August 29-30, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 17)
      - Doylestown Polish Festival, Doylestown, September 2, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 18)
      - Debate: WQED "The Editors", Pittsburgh, September 6, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 19)
      - Thornbury Corn Boil, Thornbury, September 8, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 20)
      - Pig-Roast in honor of Jay Moyer, Treasurer of Montgomery County, Ledrach, September 8, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 21)
      - Visits with Republican leaders from Beaver and Butler Counties; Interview with Print and Radio reporters, Butler, September 9, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 22)
      - Pittsburgh Italian Scholarship Fund Dinner, Pittsburgh, September 9, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 23)
      - Quad-Chamber Legislative Forum, Remarks, St. Clair, September 10, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 24)
      - Meeting with Fayette County Republican leaders, Uniontown, September 10, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 25)
      - United Way "Day of Caring" Senior Festival Days, Pittsburgh, September 11, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 26)
      - Meeting with Pro-Family Coalition of Southwest PA, Pittsburgh, September 11, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 27)
      - Chester County Republican Candidates Rally, West Chester, September 12, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 28)
      - Presidential Salute to Dick Thornburgh, with remarks by President Bush, Philadelphia, September 12, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 29)
      - Meetings with Republican leaders, Harrisburg, September 13, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 30)
      - Meetings with Republican leaders, Lancaster, September 13, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 31)
      - Third Annual Pennsylvania Leadership Conference, Remarks, Grantville, September 14, 1991 (Box 920, Folder 32)
      - Meeting with Organizations United for the Environment, McClure, September 14, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 1)
      - 100th Annual McClure Bean Soup Festival, McClure, September 14, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 2)
      - American Legion "Colonel Charles Young Day," remarks and tour, Philadelphia, September 15, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 3)
      - Fundraising breakfast hosted by Daniel Shapira, Pittsburgh, September 16, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 4)
      - Walking tours of the Lord Corporation Aerospace Plant, Gertrude Barber Center, and the Soldiers and Sailors Home, Erie, September 17, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 5)
      - Meeting with Admiral John Dalrymple, Commander of the Philadelphia Naval Base, Philadelphia, September 18, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 6)
      - Easton Area Middle School, classroom session and press conference, Easton, September 18, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 7)
      - Binney and Smith, Inc., visit with employees, meeting with management and public affairs committees, Easton, September 18, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 8)
      - Meeting with Pittsburgh Area Business Leaders, Pittsburgh, September 18, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 9)
      - Pennsylvania Small Business Trade Fair, Remarks, Monroeville, September 19, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 10)
      - Ribbon cutting ceremony for Commissioner candidates Peters and Senio, Scranton, September 19, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 11)
      - Notarianni & Company employees visit, Scranton, September 19, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 12)
      - Allied Services National Rehabilitation Week award dinner, Scranton, September 19, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 13)
      - Thornburgh for Senate Committee reception, hosted by Ralph and Joyce Lomma and Ernie Preate, Sr., Scranton, September 19, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 14)
      - Gun Rights Policy Conference, remarks, Philadelphia, September 21, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 15)
      - Super Sunday, Allentown, September 22, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 16)
      - Allegheny County Republican Family Picnic, brief remarks, Pittsburgh, September 22, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 17)
      - Pittsburgh Technology Center, tour and Economic Development Program announcement, Pittsburgh, September 23, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 18)
      - Reception in honor of European Parliament members, Pittsburgh, September 23, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 19)
      - Amen Corner, dinner and remarks, Pittsburgh, September 23, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 20)
      - ADA breakfast, "The Forging of a New Freedom Campaign," remarks, Pittsburgh, September 24, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 21)
      - Meeting with the National Association of Hispanic Elderly, Philadelphia, September 24, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 22)
      - Thornburgh for Senate Committee reception, Unionville, September 24, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 23)
      - Publicker Industries, industrial renaissance program announcement, Philadelphia, September 25, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 24)
      - Pennsylvania State Troopers Association, luncheon, remarks, Harrisburg, September 25, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 25)
      - Thornburgh for Senate Committee Schuylkill County Rally, remarks, Pottsville, September 25, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 26)
      - Pittsburgh American Association of Retired Persons meeting, remarks, Pittsburgh, September 26, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 27)
      - Thornburgh for Senate Campaign staff dinner, Pittsburgh, September 26, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 28)
      - Hollidaysburg Veterans Home, Johnstown, September 27, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 29)
      - Johnstown Corporation Production Facility, tour, economic development program press announcement, Johnstown, September 27, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 30)
      - Johnstown Tribune-Democrat editorial board meeting, Johnstown, September 27, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 31)
      - Allegheny County and Western Pennsylvania Township Officials annual conference, remarks, Champion, September 27, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 32)
      - Mt. Olivet Baptist Tabernacle church service, annual "Missionary Service," Philadelphia, September 29, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 33)
      - Home Association Bi-Annual "Pig Roast," Philadelphia, September 29, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 34)
      - Republican Women of the Main Line Candidate's event, Haverford, September 29, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 35)
      - York Dispatch editorial board meeting, and interview with print and radio reporters, York, September 30, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 36)
      - Pennsylvania League of Cities Annual Fall Conference, remarks, Harrisburg, September 30, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 37)
      - Interview with Pennsylvania Catholic Conference newspaper, Harrisburg, September 30, 1991 (Box 921, Folder 38)
      - Press availability and interviews, "Straight talk on economic development and taxes," Hershey, September 30, 1991 (Box 922, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania Chamber of Business and Industry, Hershey, September 30, 1991 (Box 922, Folder 2)
      - York Parents Against Drug Abuse and WSBA Radio Awareness Campaign Kick-Off, York, October 1, 1991 (Box 922, Folder 3)